According to 26, the Home Minister seems to me a little like if
you need it, I'll go
there and call that line and tell them to find the
timings of the earlier trains and get off.
When I
click on it, they give me the plan as of today's
date. I don't
go into the difference right now. My existing customers
can send me. I'm a one-man army.
I like my work myself.
I've hired people in my office a couple of times, but I did
n't understand their work. So
far, I'm searching to find
someone like me. I'll
put them in your running room and let them work the way I do. So,
I'm a one-man
army. I mostly deliver on health
policies and personal projects,
which are currently being called help mirrors.
Whatever policies I offer, I have
made a trap: I'll send you a
2-year help seal, a personal protection policy,
and a 3-year help seal.
In selling them, the
one-year gland requirement is, and I
force them to do it.  I had said it was for 2 years, there is nothing like that,
I tell them this benefit
that if you give this money for the second year
's installment, if you also go today, then the
reference in FD is not that much, as you are
getting discount from such banks, what do
you and I do, normally
what did we do earlier, sir, the premium is ₹2000,
if you give another 10,000, then
you will get a platter special discount, this is the
wrong way of saying, according to me,
what am I saying at the time, but 10,000, so be it
sir, if you give the next 10,000 today, you will
get 22% discount, if
you add the installment to today's date and it is late, you will have to
pay a thousand rupees, I am having diarrhea
and am on the way right now, the
disputing has reduced, in that I am
telling those people that point
five percent is in this account, if you do
28.33 likes spinner in Agra Cantt, then it
comes to 20%, tell me any prank
which  If I am 8.3% latest then I
give it, then I cross the line
and there is no such client whose client
knows that this thing has happened a lot, that
client never says no, he says
here take Ritesh Bhai Ghoshal's 3
year loan, depending upon the opposition,
Subhash Mishra is my reporting manager, my
witness, in front of you, if you
ask him percentage wise how much is Jitesh's one year
result, he will say
you get one or two percent, some points are
not in the right position, he does
not pay attention to the rate of interest of the remedy, he sees that friend, it is
necessary for me to get insurance right now and only 1 year's premium is Ravi's
address, you are getting it, does the girl do it
and what about my service, yes, this
photo of Sir came to me, it was
around 9.30 to 9.30, Jitesh Bhai,
be ready, 10:30, this is your video conferencing,
I am from Indore team and nails because she will
talk to mother, then I said tell me for what the body is, friend  There has been
some downfall of some advisors or mostly advisors
but I do
not understand what to put in and what remains and it goes out of my mind
and at this time the fun of cricket
comes only when the scores are coming within 10 days
and when you score a century, it is fun,
you should wait for that much, what are you talking about, I
mean they want to
talk about what I am, there is truth in this
and it is also true that taking 10,000, 15,000, 20,000 on
one hand means he thinks and works 10 ₹500 less
and today if he has a small
problem, he has symptoms like flour,
chest pain, a meeting, anything happens, the
hospital is changed, the
person in front, Doctor Gupta, I had
deposited 10,000 at the reception counter immediately but was
not giving the money to that person, so after
taking the money from his friend point related, he immediately
deposits it at the security level,
when the money comes from there, he deposits the money at his two places.  You
can take it there only then you can get a good position, please
explain that line, just after praising it, I am
ready to give 25 thousand fifty rupees, 1 lakh rupees immediately, when the doctor immediately tells you to do it,
if he does not relate you to him
or inside then you will not
keep the service, you are thinking of Safed Musli, I have got it done in real
life, as of today there is a health
insurance monitor, I have a
pyramid with him, before which comes Bhadra, that is the
first step of the pyramid, those are the parts, according to the
same pension planning, if there is
stomach upset in it, bread in it, it tells that
first of all it is very important for you to have health insurance, it has to be
attended, personal
accidental policy, it takes so many hours,
Kumkum Bhagya and many other things which are
not related to the meeting in this, the first thing
your son says is to have health insurance,
water tank, even today you will calculate the percentage,
I feel like
today crops 308 like do not enter into it,
okay no problem has come and our
biggest problem is what I had set, now
people tried to explain behind it and got it
transferred and got it done
People get well quickly, right now we
don't go here at the time
and nobody used to meet there, there is a meter, by
looking at the time on it we got some aspirin,
brother Gupta and other clients have to talk to that he
tells everything, I never did a
video minister Shivpal Singh Yadav did to
his teacher, I simply said sir I am
in a race, I will do
it only after completing 10 kms, I am happy with that man at that
time point Pooja, I did
not think what I should do at that time, the
evil of British meaning, I will talk to silent people, I want to
say that I would like to tell everyone what I
felt from inside, I would like to tell everyone about the
capacitor that has been sent from my feet,
I will tell everything from my heart,
how should I tell you other things, I am
not able to remember advent, simple
first point I told you that you should
focus on service, there is a
huge market, be it Nagpur or Indore, any
city where you live, it is of great
importance, the person who did not
talk to you after giving your presentation, no problem, there is a
huge market, go to another person,
go to another when the fourth  I want to go near it, it is a
very big market, it has happened to me many times
that the applicant did
not get insurance from me, after Apollo we will go to
Star, we will go to United
National, after 2 years it came back to me,
looking at me in quantity, everyone's insurance was replaced
through their insurance,
why did they come back to me, why did they take any
check service, why did they take it from my ID, Luqman
Hakim, I agree that if seen from the perspective of Teacher Wine, the
premium is not that much,
but people keep competing, the Pacific Rim
is high, hey friend, you explain to people that
Teachers and Teachers company, if you explain my premium features to my customers, they will
say brother, it is your payment, but if
you explain my premium features to my customers, it
is secondary, by God, if it comes to me, then I will
click more, I am
looking at you,
people always ask me a question in Sirsa,
that
how do you handle this type of problem at home or
what answer can you give to it, then it would be better
that I just say your ideology,
I have never done pistachio preparation,
British, you said that I give you  There is to be
an anek after 1 hour I am connected
so I don't know what else I should
talk about it is better if you also
ask some questions then I will answer them from my heart
how does it work anyway I am
telling you otherwise I have gone to
Jitendra that some people have a
question, it is a common question for everyone
I will ask you that the first question comes
regarding the price and the
price of other companies is very low the
price of ICICI Lombard which is revised now is
expensive it is a problem and it is not coming how is it getting
postponed how do you handle it
ma'am ma'am if you look at it then
when help chidne was launched in the beginning
then I also had a little problem in the settings
so I
told him in the morning that you
send me the comparison and I also checked the overall online
competition baap oil ad CID officer of
your avatar you will see write positive then
you can tell him that sir look it is doing
agrotech in which you  If you click on your ₹50 then
your no claim
bonus does not get spoiled, it is illegal,
you will see in the insurance company by competition, then
whatever I withdraw for ₹9,
it gets spoiled or the certificate on that side becomes
Namaste, it is helpless, this will
not happen here, first I will tell you this thing,
secondly I will tell you this,
then there are both expenses for
weeks, you have to understand and trouble by wasting time,
which is not there in other insurance companies,
you can comp,
if there is a daily premium but it is natural,
you can simply show them Kapil Sharma's comedy of Quality Bazaar at one o'clock,
which I have
saved, Kapil Sharma
says only one line, forget the clarification of 5 lakh rupees, the
company has sent it to the Indian market even for 7000, the
outside company does not
know that the policy is being sold in the market even for rs. 7000,
but if there is a policy of 7000,
how will it trouble you, add time and plain settlement
and the time of claim settlement,
tell them, I challenge
who is like this in Nagpur  There is an advisor who
tells me that I
filed a claim for my client against Guru Na and his claim was settled in 21 days, not
possible, I have my
own agency but I don't work for him,
but they tell me about him, I
asked him something on email, see your Kathakali singer
who has a good name in detail, he
also does good work in LIC, then he told me
that I have a policy in Pune, in Cream Daily
Star, it was for two months, there is
no clipper, I have to send mail
to the office, then after going to the office in 15 days, that
claim is getting settled in 20 days, this means that in
Alam, his claim settlement rate says that
terrorists told me that last week the device got a
virus on the mobile, till now
more than 70% of the cases in lakhs will remain healthy, so
you will see that I have taken it in time and
how many came to me and how much
addition I did in how much time, so all my fans who got angry with me
and got it by clicking on the link
and if you look at the iron side, did you pay the
full amount of the claim this month, the
₹500 registration, that  The money was received
after deducting the full amount and it was given. The last bill of 8000 was
given on 226005. You tell me something else, I am going
back. And thirdly, when
we travel from outside, we find the global
Nobel World Wide Web
in the form of thanks number, the number of
percentage price reduction is very important.
Then tell me about teachers, you will
talk openly about the customer, then he does not see 1000, 2000.
My friend does not see 1000, 2000, 3000 at all.
And secondly, if
someone comes to my work line and says that my hen will
also get the time zone, I want to take 11016, I will meet you after
maintenance. So, that
customer who is there at such a time, I
should leave it. What do we do?
Frustration arises in that customer. Hey friend, they
show me 11 lot of customers, this will reduce salivation
and motivation, why are you spoiling that? I have
15 number customers,
in return of that I have 645 these ones.  50,000 in
which it is fun to work and there is ₹3
lakh
now I feel that no, service is number one, I will
focus on service and going forward I will
do something more with Praveen and my client
never says a lot of customers,
I don't have time right now, friend,
if it doesn't matter
that here in many issues I have helped
people in real life, don't look at the cream here,
please look at Kanaram settlement, see the
percentage of settlement, how much it is giving
from the service, see the features, and the
biggest thing is that in the oldest organization in Inch and Health Insurance,
if it
is private then I
give claim settlement on the injury of the person by my ID, if you
trust your company and work with your heart
then no one can defeat you, it is never
your first feature, you should give
everything from your heart during your 24 hour service, give
family time when it is down to sleep, give walking, running, etc.,
where will I pay attention to it and those people who
tell you that you have competition,
if you get an honest customer, you should take him  You know, the
competition will take a party from Mukhandwa Khandwa on a plain paper,
if he will check your
strength, whether you will be able to provide service or not, whether
you have the guts, they replace my customers,
where is the phone and any other question, I answered the question from my house, I answered it
correctly, I mean, a lot of
people are liking it, I
mean, there is pin drop silence
in the environment, are you thinking about your Bengaluru, I mean, the
way of speaking, whatever you say from the heart, your words are reaching the
hearts of the people, so
Jitendra Bhai, I had one more question for you,
whatever current
account is being created with ISI number, December,
January, February, March, okay,
tell me something about one tip and what is your
plan for this, what should people do for this,
how should they do it, please share a little about it, what is
your opinion about it,
ICICI Lombard
's foreign trips are like this, if you
can tell me something about it,
please give me royal, from here I am doing
nonstop dance in 2018 and I have done something with my hand  There has been
no side effect in
which I have booked less than two tickets, I had booked
with these two tickets and
from Airtel Romantic Pass, whenever I had to go to any country, the
same country will be called my bad luck
but it is not my fault that I came dead body in it,
starting with Malaysia, I have
my tip in Heartless, I had already
come to this country for protection because
there also I am India's COD
advisor in life insurance, blood
group of my mother, but it got filled up completely,
my brother and sister-in-law's passport is also filled up
completely and right now they are yearning to tell
me this, should I tell you, it will
come and how much work will you do, how much is
left for me, I will get something in the morning
and then the whole thing means he does not say anything
as much as my brother, you also and does he get fuel from my mother
or not, you and there are many people in it,
I am seeing fuel Kumar Malviya ji, so right now
he means he is my close
friend, as long as he is there, enough is enough, now that is
over, now uncle  Uncle, they talk like this, mother, uncle, what
I meant to say was that
I have never seen anyone like this, I
talked about angry plate, I have done it below two tickets
and I will tell this to all the people that it is
of this thing, you will think about this chart ticket, only then
you will get two tickets,
you have that complete Hindi mentality that
even today at the restaurant or if there is no one, then
on time I was very surprised
and where do you want to know, if
someone says 10:30, then similarly the
target is fixed, if the company has
given me 40 lakh rupees
in contra voucher for 10 people, I will not leave until I get hold of it, dear, my 40 lakh
rupees, dear, my 40 lakh rupees is going to be
two digits, something else is going to happen
and you should double that target,
you should show that you have some power, you
can do everything here, you can shake the world
and secondly, what else was I saying, by the way,
Meethi had said that all the
experience of Salman Khan, maybe the Lombard
experience  I will say in one line
that you will feel like this when you edit,
then you have time, you go to him,
after that I am your seventh and sir, it is like this
in my English when
you go to the website, when you find that the
son-in-law has just come, the son-in-law is there, you get a force and
not a twist, hey you don't get up, what do
you want there, Vitamin E
dropped for watching, what do you want
according to, what do you want, by the way,
type in this all the time, if it goes,
it is a great arrangement
and our 5 minutes motivate the person's button
and we just keep
looking for 'I have come, I have clicked next', this is the
second target, the tongue will do and how much
amount will it give and how much home will I do
and how many ticket secretaries will I have to do,
and I got the answer from my ears, yes, yes, very
good, that means you completed the training of all the things which I did
not do in the last one year
in your 10-15 minutes and I would like to
thank you from the bottom of my heart, you are in
front of me, otherwise I would have hugged you, you have
said so many good things and you are
in the salon and are busy, that means everyone is seeing that
You are also getting your hair cut, still
you have done Canteen India, thank you so much, I needed you so much,
for your risk fast, whether I am in fruits
or anywhere else, I am
proud of myself, but I would also like my entire team to
definitely send it to hell,
yes, Shankar, see, the entire Indore team and the
destination of frustration loot growth has been kept in your
room, let's go, thank you so much, in continuation, it is
live on our channel right now and we were
going for tiger safari, so before doing it in the jungle,
you want to share your experience, so
this is enough to see each other,
then want to say something about you, it is
cancer, please
unmute the video,
after all, you are telling me,
hello Kanchan sir, you please unmute, I have called, I have
not unmuted, it is cancer, a
wooden box office collection, please send me a
message on WhatsApp immediately